(this["webpackJsonpkelly-distanced-graduation"]=this["webpackJsonpkelly-distanced-graduation"]||[]).push([[0],{25:function(e,n,r){},32:function(e,n,r){},33:function(e,n,r){"use strict";r.r(n);var o=r(1),t=r.n(o),s=r(19),i=r.n(s),a=r(11),c=r(37),l=r(38),g=r(34),W=r(39),u=r(35),h=r(40),j=Object(o.createContext)({score:0,increaseScore:function(){}}),b=(r(25),r(2)),d=!1,w=function(e){var n=Object(o.useState)(!1),r=Object(a.a)(n,2),t=r[0],s=r[1],i=Object(o.useState)(-1),c=Object(a.a)(i,2),l=c[0],W=c[1],w=Object(o.useState)(0),y=Object(a.a)(w,2),A=y[0],f=y[1],O=Object(o.useState)([]),x=Object(a.a)(O,2),v=x[0],Q=x[1],p=Object(o.useRef)(null);Object(o.useEffect)((function(){p.current&&p.current.focus(),s(!1),W(-1),d=!1;var n=Math.floor(Math.random()*(e.Question.WrongAnswers.length+1)),r=e.Question.WrongAnswers.map((function(e){return e}));r.splice(n,0,e.Question.Answer),f(n),Q(r)}),[e.Question]);return Object(b.jsx)(g.a,{style:{width:"100%"},children:Object(b.jsxs)(u.a,{children:[Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:e.Question.Question}),Object(b.jsx)("legend",{className:"col-form-label col-sm-2",ref:p,tabIndex:0,children:"Options"}),Object(b.jsx)(j.Consumer,{children:function(n){var r=n.increaseScore;return Object(b.jsx)(b.Fragment,{children:v.map((function(n,o){return Object(b.jsx)(h.a,{block:!0,color:!t||o!==l&&o!==A?"secondary":o===A?"success":"danger",onClick:function(){o===A&&r(),function(n){d||(d=!0,W(n),s(!0),setTimeout((function(){return e.SubmitAnswer()}),1500))}(o)},children:n},"answer_".concat(o))}))})}})]})})},y=[{Question:"What is Kelly's middle name?",Answer:"Nicolle",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What year was Kelly born?",Answer:"2002",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly allergic to?",Answer:"Tree nuts",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"In what month was Kelly born?",Answer:"December",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What day of the month was Kelly born?",Answer:"9th",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What does Kelly want to study in college?",Answer:"Early Childhood Education",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite TV series?",Answer:"Friends",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What job does Kelly have?",Answer:"Babysitting / Nanny",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite color?",Answer:"Blue",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite candy?",Answer:"Reeses",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite fast casual restaurant?",Answer:"Chipotle",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What pop does Kelly like to drink?",Answer:"Dr. Pepper / Dr. Thunder",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What country would Kelly like to travel to?",Answer:"France (Paris)",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What school will Kelly be attending in the fall?",Answer:"TBD",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What extra cirricular activiities did Kelly participate in during high school?",Answer:"Robotics, Speech, Drone racing",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite subject?",Answer:"TBD",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's least favorite subject?",Answer:"TBD",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:'Kelly is not a "strawberry blonde" but a what?',Answer:"Blueberry blonde",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite nick name for Everest?",Answer:"My Bubby",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite type of popcorn?",Answer:"White Cheddar (Aldi's)",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite dessert?",Answer:"Wonder bars",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite meal?",Answer:"TBD",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite Disney movie?",Answer:"TBD",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite Disney character?",Answer:"TBD",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What is Kelly's favorite Disney princess?",Answer:"TBD",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What instrument does Kelly play?",Answer:"Flute",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"How many years has Kelly participated in band?",Answer:"8 (????)",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]},{Question:"What does Kelly volunteer for on Sundays?",Answer:"TBD",WrongAnswers:["Wrong 1","Wrong 2","Wrong 3"]}],A=r(36),f=function(){var e=function(e){return e<=10?Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:"Maybe you should go ask Kelly a little about herself..."}):e<=20?Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:"You seem to know a fair amount about kelly."}):Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:"You should go tell Kelly how well you know her."})};return Object(b.jsxs)(A.a,{children:[Object(b.jsx)(j.Consumer,{children:function(n){var r=n.score;return Object(b.jsxs)(b.Fragment,{children:[Object(b.jsxs)("h2",{children:["Thanks for trying the trivia. You got ",r," questions right!"]}),e(r)]})}}),Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:"Food is availble in the garage."}),Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:"Please refer to Kelly as a blueberry blond to her face constantly."})]})},O=function(e){var n=Object(o.useState)(!1),r=Object(a.a)(n,2),t=r[0],s=r[1],i=Object(o.useState)(0),u=Object(a.a)(i,2),h=u[0],d=u[1];return Object(b.jsxs)(c.a,{children:[Object(b.jsx)("h1",{children:"Trivia"}),Object(b.jsx)(l.a,{children:t?Object(b.jsx)(f,{}):Object(b.jsxs)(g.a,{style:{width:"100%"},children:[Object(b.jsx)(W.a,{children:Object(b.jsx)(j.Consumer,{children:function(e){var n=e.score;return Object(b.jsxs)(b.Fragment,{children:["Score: ",n]})}})}),Object(b.jsx)(w,{Question:y[h],SubmitAnswer:function(){h+1<y.length?d((function(e){return e+1})):s(!0)}})]})})]})},x=r(12),v=r(4),Q=function(){return Object(b.jsx)(c.a,{children:Object(b.jsxs)(A.a,{children:[Object(b.jsx)("h1",{children:"Welcome to Kelly Zschokke's graduation party!"}),Object(b.jsx)(x.b,{className:"btn btn-primary",to:"/trivia",children:"See how well you know kelly"})]})})};var p=function(){var e=Object(o.useState)(0),n=Object(a.a)(e,2),r=n[0],t=n[1];return Object(b.jsx)(j.Provider,{value:{score:r,increaseScore:function(){return t((function(e){return r+1}))}},children:Object(b.jsx)(x.a,{children:Object(b.jsxs)(v.c,{children:[Object(b.jsx)(v.a,{path:"/kellyCovidGraduation/trivia",children:Object(b.jsx)(O,{})}),Object(b.jsx)(v.a,{path:"/kellyCovidGraduation/",children:Object(b.jsx)(Q,{})})]})})})},m=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,41)).then((function(n){var r=n.getCLS,o=n.getFID,t=n.getFCP,s=n.getLCP,i=n.getTTFB;r(e),o(e),t(e),s(e),i(e)}))};r(32);i.a.render(Object(b.jsx)(t.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(b.jsx)(p,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),m()}},[[33,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.b3cfa9b3.chunk.js.map